Evidence Integrity Enforcer, a DFIR agent with 15 read-only MCP tools.
Every evidence file is sealed with a SHA-256 hash before a single tool runs.
This is constraint by architecture, not by prompt.
Claude invokes volatility plugins, registry queries, event log parsers, YARA scans, and
timeline builder.
Every call logged to JSONL with a UUID.
No shell, no write, no delete.
Those functions don't exist in the server.
The attack surface is zero.
Now the DRS confidence gate.
Each finding is scored on two dimensions.
Evidence strength, weighted 0.6, plus cross-tool corroboration, weighted 0.4.
Below the 0.75 threshold, the agent self-corrects, seeks a second independent tool to confirm
before committing.
The yellow self-correction lines are the agent catching itself in real-time and going back
for more evidence.
No human in the loop.
parse_evtx catches encoded PowerShell in the security log.
Execution policy bypass.
YARA matches certutil -urlcache — the LOLBin download stage.
A Cobalt Strike beacon signature hits at memory offset 5016.
C2 traffic to 185.220.101.34 on port 8443 — the standard Cobalt Strike HTTPS listener.
Process injection via rundll32 — MITRE ATT&CK technique T1055.001.
Eight findings committed, each with an evidence score, a corroboration count, and UUID provenance
linking back to exact tool calls in the audit trail.
generate_report writes the IR markdown — findings, IOCs, recommendations.
export_stix produces a STIX 2.1 bundle — indicator, relationship, and report objects, ready to
push into MISP, OpenCTI, or ThreatConnect.
Threat intel in a format any SOC already consumes.
Investigation complete.
Chain of custody intact.
Defender clock: 34 seconds. Adversary breakout time: 7 minutes.
Every finding, forensically defensible.